http://www.imres.nl/en/page/privacy-policy

Jump past the navigationHomeAbout usOur CustomersTeamCareersSuppliersHistorySustainabilityShow allSolutionsEmergency ResponseOne Stop ShopTurn-key SolutionsShow allProductguidesMedical KitsPharmaceuticalsMedical ConsumablesMedical InstrumentsHospital and Doctors Room EquipmentDiagnosticsShow allQualityQuality AssuranceQuality ControlCode of ConductShow allLogisticsTailored SolutionsWarehousePackingShow allNewsImres supplies Covid-19 general treatment kits to the WHOCOVID-19 update and FAQStatement on COVID-19 outbreakNew managing director for imres1 in 10 medical products in developing countries is substandard or falsifiedThe European Falsified Medicines DirectiveShow allContactLanguage ENAbout usContactNewsTerms & conditionsPrivacy policyCookie policyLog in0
My account0Log inLanguage ENEnglishFrenchPortugueseHomeAbout usOur CustomersTeamCareersSuppliersHistorySustainabilitySolutionsEmergency ResponseOne Stop ShopTurn-key SolutionsProductguidesMedical KitsPharmaceuticalsMedical ConsumablesMedical InstrumentsHospital and Doctors Room EquipmentDiagnosticsQualityQuality AssuranceQuality ControlCode of ConductLogisticsTailored SolutionsWarehousePackingNewsImres supplies Covid-19 general treatment kits to the WHOCOVID-19 update and FAQStatement on COVID-19 outbreakNew managing director for imres1 in 10 medical products in developing countries is substandard or falsifiedThe European Falsified Medicines DirectiveContact Your privacy with ImresYour privacy with Imres
Imres B.V. treats all information collected on our website as confidential. Our privacy policy outlines how we collect this information and use it throughout our website. Information is collected by specifically engaging with you, this occurs when you subscribe to our newsletter and mailing list or e-mail or contact us directly.
Use of
information collected on the site
We want to help you maintain your privacy on the Internet. We will treat your information in total confidence and will only share your information with our affiliates, subsidiaries, alliance partners and service providers required to be given access to the information. We will not sell or rent this information to any other third-parties.
What personal data is being processed by Imres?
If you request for a login on our website, request a brochure or subscribe to our newsletter we will store the following data:
•	Company name
•	Name
•	Email address
•	Company address
•	Company phone number
•	CoC number
•	VAT number
Legal ground / Consent
The information which we collect from you may be used for a variety of reasons, such as:
•	Allowing you to access the enclosed part of our website
•	Allowing you to receive our newsletter with information on our products and services
•	establishing the general demographics, statistics or market information;
•	to compile a broad profile of visitors who access and transact via the site;
•	responding to queries you may have asked the Provider through the website; and
•	providing the User with a catalogue of the Provider’s new products and services from time to time.
By requesting an account, brochure or subscribing to our newsletter you agree that we store the personal data mentioned above. Please note that all information is aggregated, therefore no identifiable individual or company information is shared with other parties.
Right to access / rectification or erasure of your personal data
At all times you have the right to access, rectify or have your data erased from our servers. Just send an email to PPO@imres.nl .
Data Security
Communication with the Imres website is encrypted using SSL technology.
Social Media
Please note that on the website the Provider has links to its Social Media Pages. A User must be aware that any information or material he/she may post on the Provider’s social media pages will become public information. The User must be careful of the material or information he/she posts on the Providers social media pages. The Provider shall not be held liable for any information or material the User publishes on the Provider’s social media pages through the Provider’s website.
Promotional emails
Should you elect to be added to our mailing list or subscribe to our newsletter we use the information we collect to better meet your needs by sending you information on latest news and new services which may be of interest to you. From time to time we will email you information about us, if you do not wish to receive this e-mail you can opt out by unsubscribing or e-mailing us. Please refer to our contact e-mail addresses below.
When we will disclose / share personal data
We will only disclose personal data both within and outside the EU if required to do so by law or if it is required to protect the safety of our customers or the public, or if we believe that such action is necessary to protect and defend our rights (or any of our affiliates), safety, privacy or property.
Cookies and Storage of information
Imres may from time to time make use of cookies. Cookies allows a web-server to collect information about the User for purposes amongst others, described above under Use of information collected on the site. It will solely be on the discretion of the User to either accept or refuse cookies through the settings on its internet web browser or alternatively use a programme or application to control the use of cookies by any website.
Information collected by us via the site is stored in a secure operating environment that is not available to the public. Imres saves the information up to 14 months and will erase it after that period. For more information about our cookie policy please click here.
Hyperlinks to Third-Party websites
This web-site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies adopted by these websites. The inclusion of any links on our website does not imply recommendation or endorsement by the Provider or any of its affiliates. Use of or reliance by the User of any links on the website is at the Users own risk.
A User is prohibited from creating any links to the website without the prior written consent from the Provider.
Updates and Amendments to Privacy Policy
Provider reserves the right without notice to change, modify, amend, add to or remove portions or whole parts of this Privacy Policy from time to time permanently or temporarily. All updates and/or amendments to the Privacy Policy are effective on the date the Provider publishes them on the website. The responsibility is on the User to determine whether any updates and/or amendments have been made to the Privacy Policy. The continued use of the website by the User after the updates or amendments have been made to the Privacy Policy has the effect of the User agreeing to be bound by the new terms of the Privacy Policy.
Password Protected Areas
The Website has password protected areas and these areas are restricted to authorised Users. It is the Users responsibility to keep his/her login credentials confidential. The Provider shall not be held responsible for any acts or omissions committed by the User and/or third parties in relation to the password protected areas on the website.
Severability
In the event that only part of this Privacy Policy are found to be invalid, unlawful or unenforceable, such terms shall be severable from the remaining Privacy Policy, which shall remain valid and enforceable.
Indulgence
Any indulgence, leniency or extension of time which the Provider may give to the User shall not operate as an estoppel or in any way prejudice the Provider or preclude the Provider from exercising any of its rights in the future.
Whole Agreement
The Privacy Policy expressed above constitutes the whole agreement and the Provider and User are bound by the Privacy Policy herein.
Queries
If you have any queries in relation to this Privacy Policy, please contact us on: PPO@imres.nl
Stay informed of news & promotionsThis content is not visible because of your cookie settings.Accept cookiesAbout usContactNewsTerms & conditionsPrivacy policyCookie policyLarserpoortweg 268218 NK LelystadNetherlands+31 (0)320-296969info@imres.nl+31 (0)320-296929+31 (0)320 296969Language*EnglishFrenchPortugueseSave preferencesName*Password* These values are stored in a cookie.Log inI forgot my passwordI don't have an account yetName*Send me a password-reset linkLog inWe use cookies just to track visits to our website, we store no personal details. Please refer to our
Cookie Policy. and our Privacy Policy.Accept cookiesDecline cookiesCloseNo permission to request location.Location not available.Timeout during location request.Error during location request.Ok
